We will see the importance of the eye in the expression of the cranio-sacral system
頭蓋仙骨系の表現における眼の重要性を見ていきます
and in neuronal memorization and also in tissue memorization.
そして神経の記憶、さらに組織の記憶においても。
This means that you can store memories anywhere in your body
これは、体のどこにでも記憶を置くことができるという意味です
that are written by the eye.
それは目によって書かれています。
If you don't know, for example, how to integrate them, you will somatize them.
例えば、それらを統合する方法を知らない場合、あなたはそれらを身体化するでしょう。
What is not integrated is somatized.
統合されていないものは身体化されます。
Every time there is an eye, there is an eye, there is an eye.
目があるたびに、目があり、目があります。
that I don't know how to solve a problem
心配事を解決できないとき
my body will memorize it
私の体はそれを記憶するでしょう
but in its symbolism
しかし、その象徴性において
in its symbolism
その象徴性において
where it will memorize it according to the spaces
空間に応じてそれを記憶する場所
that is, of space
つまり、空間の
mineral, plant, animal
鉱物、植物、動物
or human
または人間
depending on the timing
タイミングに応じて
and the processes of coordination and synchronicity
そして協調と同期のプロセス
so you're going to synchronize it
だからあなたはそれを同期させるでしょう
in your symbolism
あなたの象徴性において
you're going to symbolize it
あなたはそれを象徴するでしょう
I'm three years old
私は3歳です
and then you're going to put it in your symbolism
そしてあなたはそれをあなたの象徴性に入れるでしょう
And I'm really scared.
そして私はとても怖いです。
My parents are leaving.
両親が出かけます。
They leave me alone at home.
彼らは私を家に一人残します。
I panicked.
私はパニックになりました。
I'm going to hide under the table.
私はテーブルの下に隠れます。
And then all of a sudden, I catch what we call colds.
そして突然、いわゆる風邪をひきます。
I have maxillary sinuses.
上顎洞があります。
And in fact, we see that there is a synchronicity.
そして実際、同期があることがわかります。
in the pneumatization spaces between the
間の気化空間において
adrenals and my maxillary sinuses.
副腎と上顎洞。
And later, this person comes with chronic sinusitis.
そして後で、この人は慢性副鼻腔炎で来ます。
She symbolized an unresolved problem.
彼女は未解決の問題を象徴しました。
This is not where it is treated.
ここで治療するものではありません。
It is treated by releasing your adrenals.
治療は、副腎を解放することです。
Because what did the adrenals do?
なぜなら、副腎は何をしたのでしょうか？
They have two...
彼らは2つ持っています...
cortisol movement
コルチゾールの動きで
in relation to stress.
ストレスと関連して。
You're going to increase it.
あなたはそれを増やすでしょう。
But there, you don't know how to do it well.
しかし、あなたはそれをうまく行う方法を知りません。
So, your adrenals are blocked.
したがって、あなたの副腎はブロックされています。
Fears, in fact,
実際、恐れは、
it's not so much the kidney.
腎臓そのものではありません。
It's the cap on the kidneys.
それは腎臓の上にある帽子です。
Same thing with, for example,
例えば、甲状腺と前頭洞も同じです。
the thyroid and the frontal sinus.
甲状腺と前頭洞も同じです。
Around 7 years old,
7歳頃になると、
I know how to do it
私はできるようになります。
front, by my voice, because the activity
私の声によって、なぜなら、
electrical activity of the lateroid is fully functional,
側頭葉の電気活動が完全に機能しているからです。
that is to say, my vocal cords, my words have strength. And
つまり、私の声帯、私の言葉には力があります。そして、
then there is still
もう一つあります。
another one, it's the brain that descends into the testicles, around 12
それは、約12歳頃に、脳が睾丸に降りてくることです。
years old, where
約12歳頃に、
we have what we call the pituitary phenomenon, in relation to
私たちは下垂体現象と呼ばれるものを持っています。これは、
pituitary pneumatization,
下垂体の気化と関連しています。
the puberty axis, so these are
思春期の軸、つまりホルモンです。
hormones, it happens
それは同時に起こり、
at the same time, it will mature
性腺を成熟させ、
and allow the transformation of spermatozoa
精子の変態を可能にします。
These are spaces of synchronicity.
これらは同期の空間です。
In other spaces, you have spaces
他の空間には、象徴化の空間があります。
symbolization. Sometimes,
象徴化の空間があります。時には、
these are people who are stuck in time.
時間の中で立ち往生している人々がいます。
In fact, sometimes you can be stuck when you have
実際、時には、あなたが持っているときに立ち往生することがあります。
You have a point, an anchor,
あなたはポイント、アンカーを持っています。
and every time there is a phenomenon
そして、現象があるたびに、
you reactivate the visual memory
視覚的記憶を再活性化します。
or auditory, but it's very visual
または聴覚的記憶を再活性化しますが、それは非常に視覚的です。
people have images
人々はイメージを持っています。
you see
ほら、
and then we use these images
そして、私たちはこれらのイメージを使います。
in a technique that is very nice
とても素晴らしいテクニックで、
it's what we call rapid eye movement
それは私たちが急速眼球運動と呼ぶものです。
that we do at night
夜に行うもので、
to try to resolve
解決しようとします。
and set up the system
そしてシステムを確立します。
and we use this in a technique called EMDR
そして、MDRと呼ばれるテクニックでそれを使います。
so it doesn't remove the trauma
だから、それはトラウマを取り除くものではありません。
but it gives you back this dissociation
しかし、それはあなたにその解離を取り戻させます。
this non-identification
その非同一化を。
but in fact these are memories
しかし、実際にはこれらは記憶です。
and we do it with what? with the eyes
そして、私たちは何を使ってそれを行うのでしょうか？目を使って。
why will the eye make these movements?
なぜ目がこれらの動きをするのでしょうか？
because it will go from your left brain
それは、あなたの左脳から
to your right brain
あなたの右脳へと移行するからです。
it will put back in the right box
それは適切な場所に再配置します。
what is between the rational and the irrational
合理的と非合理的なものの間にあるものを。
between what is rational
合理的なものと
and intuitive
直感的なものの間にあるものを。
you see?
わかりますか？
an imbalance
不均衡。
someone who...
誰かが...
too rational
あまりにも合理的すぎると、
will have an imbalance
不均衡を抱えることになります。
pituitary.
下垂体の。
Someone who is
誰かが
too intuitive all the time
常に直感的すぎると、
will have a pituitary imbalance.
下垂体の不均衡を抱えることになります。
It's like riding a bicycle.
それは自転車に乗るようなものです。
The pituitary gland,
下垂体は、
it tries to do all that
これらすべてを行おうとします。
vis-à-vis the corpus callosum system
脳梁系に関して、
to pass on the information.
情報を伝達するために。
In fact, it's a lot of information
実際、それは大きな情報です。
that passes with the visual areas
視覚野を介して伝達される、
in relation to eye movement.
目の動きに関して。
that rebalance.
それが再均衡させます。
They go tac, tac, tac, tac, tac, tac,
彼らはタッタッタッタッタッと動きます。
and we do that every night.
そして、私たちは毎晩それを行います。
I take, tac, all my baggage,
私はすべての荷物を取り、
I rationalize, I put back,
合理化し、再配置します。
or I'm intuitive, I put back in the boxes.
あるいは、直感的になり、適切な場所に再配置します。
Dreaming is very important.
夢は非常に重要です。
And we can use these eye movements,
そして、私たちはこれらの目の動きを使うことができます。
like heart coherence,
心臓のコヒーレンスのように、
and things like that, all of that is important.
そしてそのようなもの、これらすべてが重要です。